Maybe I should try making it a little stronger.
ちょっと強くしてみようかな
It feels really good here.
ここめっちゃ気持ちいい
It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
Yay.
イエーイ
My impression has changed.
印象変わりましたね
I went a little blonde.
ちょっと金髪にしちゃいました
What do you think?
どうですか?
It's like fejeon.
こんかフェジョンみたい
Yes, but I won't tell you what I'm doing.
そう、でも何してるかの内緒です
I'm a maid today.
メイドだもんね、今日は
Since she's a maid, I thought it was a fejeon.
メイドだからこんかフェジョンって思って
Clubhouse.
会所
Wait a minute, then don't stand still.
ちょっと じゃあ、立っておらなくて
Is it okay?
いいの?
Is it burnt?
先焼けかな?
this.
これ
Huh, is that so?
え、そうなのかな?
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
How's your butt?
お尻どう?
Half blood, half blood.
半血、半血
Oh, that's embarrassing.
え、恥ずかしい
difficult.
難しい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I think this looks close.
これ近いに見えちゃいそう
What do you think?
どうですか?
Today is the first time in a while.
今日は久々ですけど
Wow, it's been a long time since I last saw Edge.
え、めっちゃ久々のエッジなんですよ
Please be kind to me uncle.
ちょっとおじさん優しくしてくださいよ
Really?
本当に?
Yeah, not really.
そう、めっちゃしてない
How much?
ど れくらい?
Well, I haven't been for about 2 or 3 months.
え、2、3ヶ月くらいしてない
2 or 3 months?
2、3ヶ月?
Please be a little gentler.
ちょっと優しくしてください
Hibiki-chan: That's right, it's kind of small.
ひ び きちゃんあれだよね、なんか狭いもんね
Yes, because the sound is narrow.
そう、ひびき狭いから
I want you to be a little kinder to me, because my uncle is big.
ちょっと優しくしてほしい、おじさんの大きいから
Please be a little gentle.
ちょっと優しくね
Please be a little gentler.
ちょっと優しくしてください
I'm going.
行きます
Oh, wait, it's still big.
え、待って、相変わらず大きいね
Eh, it's moving now.
え、動いてる、今
Try touching it.
触ってみてさ
What, can I touch you?
え、触っていいの?
Oh, it's already ticking.
え、もうカチカチ
Great, it's still big.
やばい、相変わらず大きい
Looks like it's already sold.
もう売りそうですね
Well, it's been a while, after all.
え、久々なんですよ、だって
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
please.
どうぞ
delicious.
おいしい
Delicious as always.
相変わらずおいしい
Oh, wait, it's been a while.
え、これ待って、久々なんですけど
Well, it's been a long time since I've felt nervous.
え、超久々、緊張する
He doesn't even bellow.
おなりもしないんだ
Yeah, I did it recently.
うん、最近してな
Yes, it's been a while.
そう、どっか久々にする
Can I use it?
使っていい?
I like it.
好きなのね
Eh, it's too strong.
え、強すぎる
Too strong.
強すぎる
I guess I'll try to tempt you first.
ちょっと最初は誘惑しよっかな
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Even if it's quite inviting, it might be just right.
結構誘わくてもちょうどいいかも
I like it.
好きなのね
No, it looks like I'll be leaving soon.
いや、これすぐ行っちゃいそうだよ
This feels good.
気持ちいい、これ
I like phone calls.
電話好きなんですよ、私
I guess I'll try making it a little stronger.
ちょっと強くしてみよっかな
Long time no see.
久々
Feels good.
気持ちいい
No, I might go for that.
いや、 それ行っちゃうかも
Well, no matter what.
え、いいっても
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Manzuri is also available.
マンズリも出てる
Wait, really?
え、待って、本当に?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Please give me back my pussy.
マンズリ返ししといて
It's been used for a long time.
久々に使われるの
A little manly.
ちょっとマンズリ
I'm getting a little sensitive.
ちょっと敏感になってる
Manzuri?
マンズリか
マンズリ?
Are they scattered?
散らされてる?
Spread your pussy open.
マンズリ広げて
yeah?
ん?
Spread your pussy open.
マンズリ広げて
From behind.
後ろから
From behind?
後 ろから?
You can help me.
手どかしていいよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
Shall we shake it?
揺らしてみる?
Don't close it, it will fall out.
閉めないで、抜けちゃうから
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Well, this is my first time.
え、初めてこれ
It's shaking.
揺らしてますね
Well, this is my first time.
え、初めてこれ
Wow, it feels good.
すごい、気持ちいい
Is something shaking?
なんか揺れてる?
Yeah, amazing.
うん、すごい
Maybe it could be stronger.
もっと強くてもいいかも
picture?
え?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
At first?
最初は?
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
It's dangerous in the back.
奥やばい
Oh, I'm going to say this.
あ っていっちゃう、これ
Chau?
ちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Because I will receive it.
受け取るから
Soaked.
びちょびちょ
Manjul is amazing.
マンジュルがすごい
Manjul is out.
マンジュル出ちゃった
Anal is amazing, but will it recover?
アナルもすごいけど、回復する?
Oh, really?
え、 ほんと?
Wow, that's really embarrassing.
え、ほんと恥ずかしい
Well, it's been a while since I licked my dick.
え、久々にチクビ舐めます
You can lick it, uncle.
舐めちゃっていい、おじさんの
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
It tastes kind of sweet.
なんか甘い味がします
I wonder if they also serve rice balls?
おにぎりでも出てるのかな?
Maybe so.
そうかも
of body soap.
ボディーソープの
Can I lick this too?
こっちも舐めていいの?
Can I touch your penis?
チンチン触っていい?
Yeah.
うん
Uncle is getting really hard.
お じ さんめっちゃ硬くなってるよ
That's dangerous.
やばいじゃん
Well then, please do me a favor.
じゃあ ちょっとお願いしまーす
Can I lick it?
舐めていいんですか?
It's big.
おっきいですね
You can add it from there.
そっから加えてくれますね
Can I lick your balls?
たま舐めていいんですか?
that's right.
そう です
I'll lick it for the first time in a while.
久々に舐めます
Did you come to the hole?
穴にきたっけ?
Can I lick your balls?
たま舐めていいんですか?
I'll lick it for the first time in a while.
久々に舐めます
I'm going to lick your hole.
穴を舐めちゃいまーす
Spread it out and lick it.
広げて舐めるんだね
Yeah, is that so?
ええ、そうなんの?
No?
だめ?
no.
いや
No taste?
味がくない?
Yeah.
うん
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おい しい?
Was it hentai?
ヘンタイだったっけ?
Yeah?
ええ?
Was it this hentai?
こんなにヘンタイだったっけ?
I'm excited because it's been a while.
久々だから興奮してます
No taste?
味がくない?
Yeah.
うん
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おい しい?
Was it hentai?
ヘンタイだったっけ?
Yeah?
ええ?
Was it this hentai?
こんなにヘンタイだったっけ?
I'm excited because it's been a while.
久々だから興奮してます
Then I'm going to lick your uncle's dick.
じゃあ おじさんのチンチン舐めちゃいまーす
You look happy.
嬉しそうですね
Yeah?
ええ?
Did you find out?
バレました?
Do you want it in quickly?
早く入れてほしいですか?
Yeah?
ええ?
secret.
内緒
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいですか?
Yeah.
うん
You look happy.
嬉しそうですね
Do you want it in quickly?
早く入れてほしいですか?
Yeah?
ええ?
secret.
内緒
once again.
もう一度
Let's go again.
もう一度行こう
This is the first Edge of the year.
今年初エッジです
First edge.
初エッジ
terrible.
やばい
I want it to come in soon.
早く入れてほしい
But I'm a little nervous.
でもちょっと緊張してる
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
The dillidly from earlier was thick.
さ っきのディリドリー太いですよ
Does it hurt?
痛いかな?
Because my uncle is big.
おじさんの大きいから
Just take it easy.
ちょっとじゃあゆっくり
please take it easy.
ゆっくりしてください
Please be kind.
優しくしてください
While.
しながら
Just one piece.
さっき一丁です
Did you just get one?
さっき一丁なの?
With this.
これで
It's big.
大きいですね
There's nothing.
なにかおらず
Half, half.
半分、半分
Even though it's been a long time since I've had an edge.
久 々のエッジなのに
half.
半分
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Can I move slowly?
ゆっくり動かしてはいい?
Take it slow at first.
ちょっと最初はゆっくり
Feels good.
気持ちいい
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
Does it look like this?
こうやって見える?
appear.
見える
Feels good.
気持ちいい
There.
そこ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'll put it in at the top.
上位で入れちゃいます
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Move forward a little.
ちょっと前側になって
May I?
いいですか?
What if I turn right?
右向ければ?
Yeah.
うん
The one in the back.
後ろの方が
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Move forward a little.
ちょっと前側になって
May I?
いいですか?
intense.
激しい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
terrible.
やばい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
I think I'm going to go.
行っちゃいそう
Then I'll go.
そんなしたら行っちゃう
Hey, I'm going.
やべ、行っちゃう
I'm going.
行っちゃう
Shall we go?
行 っちゃう?
terrible.
や ばい
appear?
見える?
picture?
え?
That camera.
あっちカメラ
appear.
見える
It's in.
入ってます
real?
ほんと?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
appear?
見える?
This way.
こっち
It feels good there.
そこ気持ちいい
Who has it?
持った人いい?
Okay.
いいよ
Just the upper body here.
上半身だけこっち
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I went deep into it.
深いそこに入っちゃった
Well then, just a little.
じゃあちょっと
That's up to the fourth one.
4つ目までだよ
Because I'm going to eat carrots.
人参しちゃうからな
How was it?
どうでした?
Have you had sex for the first time in a while?
久しぶりのセックスは?
I felt it more than usual.
いつもより感じちゃいました
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
It was amazing.
すごかったね
I ate a lot.
いっぱい食いちゃった